All right, we'll call it to order the regular scheduled city council meeting for Monday, October 21st.
To give it on schedule personal passes, have none three claims, Mr. Bruce, I have.
Uh, Parker.
Thank you.
Hi.
He's dead.
All right.
Four.
Benjamin number 25.
That's five.
General fund transferring past library donation money to the grant donation fund.
Library correcting and increasing their carryover and creating the expenses.
As required by library staff, we're in company far to part of the money used to pay for this
Get unit for the new brush truck purchased in fiscal year 2324.
Yes, so to board has any questions.
Staff here to answer any questions I want to do.
I think Chris is excited about.
What is this get unit?
It's uh, for a rest.
I decided to say motion number.
Second.
Parker.
Thank you.
He's dead.
And birds.
Five.
We're going with.
Like Larry Harris.
For.
To place project app.
In the amount of $3,900 which will allow patrons to access electronic content and all
the city manager design.
So this we budgeted into our budget for this year from materials.
I was able to work with a current vendor that we have and they lowered our renewal from
$6,500 to $2,900 so that I would have the extra money to do this app this year.
It'll bring all of our electronic stuff into one half and it also includes adding more content.
So e-books, audio books.
I kind of stuff so that they can patrons can access it with one out.
The set of five.
I think you got her vote.
I'll make a motion to approve.
I'm sorry.
Parker.
Hi.
Dougal.
E-step.
Hi.
And birds.
Thank you.
Six.
Resolution.
Hello.
Plus Parker.
To you district one seat.
The Board of Directors.
For the Alcohol and Municipality.
Declaring Set.
appointment to be for the benefit of the city of Malmukhama and other municipalities within
the district and the Claring of the Mission of the Oklahoma Municipal E to be the public purpose.
So bless us to express interest in serving in the district one seat that is vacated.
And so there was a deadline of the 18th, but I contacted OML and they said,
because we didn't have a meeting and we didn't need to have a special meeting.
And so as long as they get this, I'll send it if you so prove it.
And then now all the other required documents I sent already.
So we just have to send this for his nomination to go forward.
So, but they were fine with it being a little late.
Most two proofs.
I didn't.
Okay, park, parker.
You abstain.
Uncle.
Hi.
Eastiff.
Ann Barnes.
Seven award beds C-24-81 to Scott construction to complete the remediation and restoration
of the public works building as recommended by staff and a pretty contract.
Take it upon this mission of all required contract documents.
We saw proposals to select construction company.
The media and restore the public works building.
We posted the solicitation to the public and sand RFPs.
We received proposals from two companies.
One is any time roofing.
The other is Scott construction.
Scott construction was the lowest better.
And you can see the priceless down below.
We will be using Scott construction for an RFM.
The project with an RFM roof versus a standing seam.
They came in at 183-288.
Any time roofing came in at 271.
And we recommend awarding Scott construction for the business for 183,288.
This is part of that fire rehab.
For a back end.
This will take out all the insulation installed in the roof.
And for $400 on and over the solar side that part of that.
So will the insurance money cover all that?
Insurance money will cover this.
I'll make a motion.
We approve.
Parker.
Uncle.
He's still.
I.
Bart.
Eight award bid C24-86 to Whitney Manufacturing for a metal building kit.
To be used for mechanics building.
It's recommended by staff and approve the contract ticket.
Upon the submission of all required.
I just realized I am two of the same B.A.s.
Do we have another copy up here?
I think no criminal.
This is the replacement of the building
that since we couldn't really been built back on that E.S.
If you remember, we did that out earlier before
and it came back and contractors really had issues
with building back on that same pad.
So this is for a kit to move in the canics building off side.
Now, we're going to go 40 by 100 to 100 by 100.
We'll just get set next to the street bar down there.
This is for the kit only.
And then we will go through the will be our own prime
to do all the steps to have a built.
We'll have our own concrete, electricity, stuff.
So we'll be between the street bar and the...
Animal shelter.
Yeah.
It's a little bigger.
I'm got it right here.
You've got it?
Yeah.
I think they...
Yep.
And the other company was Builders Unlimited
and it came in 2.42,874.
The difference in those two,
this was Builders Unlimited.
They included the garage doors.
But when we went out and moved it,
doing the garage doors are our own.
It's about 38 to 40,000.
So we were still laying out there with it.
But those numbers are really pushed on there.
All right.
It's got the Whitney and the Builders.
The things swapped a little bit.
But on the bottom of it, it confirms the pricing.
So...
I mean, exactly.
Whitney, it's a backward jab.
Yeah, Whitney's actually the 121.
Right.
If you're always low.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, I'll make a motion.
We approved Whitney at 121, 1991.
I'll just look at it.
Then we're aggressive, dude.
I'm okay.
Parker?
Hi.
Uncle?
Estep?
In Bart's.
I don't know how you do that.
Or Bart?
That's correct.
If you're listening, he said that there was broad stores included.
But now ourselves were about $40,000.
Yeah, that's still $70,000.
It's different.
Even that.
Thanks guys.
Good job.
Sometimes people don't.
9.
The new business of any of which is written so it's posting a list of gender.
So, Council, this is just to give you a hint, but recent events, this afternoon, they're
going to report the proposals for the show and to the members of the board.
However, one of the bidding entities fly home, aviation, through their bid, things have a
little testy, also said that they were giving a 30-day notice of their intent to cancel the
contract with the city, as far as we know, there is no contract with the various things
that happened there.
We asked them to move out, and it's been as possible, said that they could do the worst
of the worst.
It isn't a city's plan to block tomorrow, if they still have some other things that you
can do.
So, anyway, this is just to give you the hints of what was going on, this was a significant
change from what we thought was going to be had in chess.
10 staff reports, well I guess there's any bad any questions for Bill on that, 10 staff reports, 11
Mayor, Council, Community and Management.
Probably not, was fun, homemade treat, it was a blast, well done, it was a great event.
I made mention that, and I wish you do it once a month.
And if we got to pull it inside, we'd shoot upstairs in the ballroom, whether it's not
good.
And the ball rod went over real well too.
It was a good time for an I at Bull rod and what well.
You know, Tyler and I, after the Bull rod event, were contacted by a potential business coming
to town, it happens every time.
we have and then it seems like people notice. They have the same software we have. They know
when large numbers of people gather in an area, they see when it happens, they call them
on a Y. We've got some really good potential stuff off of that. We can't say a whole lot
of rough top for heads, but the one thing that we do that I do want to say publicly is
one of these entities when we were talking to them, we talked to them about the Turnpike
area because we hear that all the time and people are like, why don't we have a turnpike, why don't
we have a turnpike, and we push everybody that direction, but everybody always comes back to
Main Street, they want to be on Main Street, and they want to compete.
And this guy said the same thing, I want to be on Main Street, because I want to compete.
But the one thing he told us about the Turnpike area, which made sense to us, he said,
nobody wants to be that flagship. When you're that flagship, you're sitting there by yourself.
And he said, we've been in that situation before, and we've been in an area just like that.
We were the flagship, and he said instead of us paying ourselves back in three years, it took six years
because we was out there by ourselves, there was nobody to compete with.
They want to go over, they have choices, they want to go over, they can compete.
So, it made sense to us, because we've tried to push people that direction and nobody ever bites.
Nobody wants to take that leap, but it made sense when he explained it to us that nobody wants to be that
flagship and take that risk with their money. They would rather take that risk with their money down on our strip,
or Main Street, where everybody else is at, because that's where everybody's going.
So, it kind of opened our eyes, I think, because we've never really heard anybody explain to us that way before.
But people are still noticing us, the Popeyes people, I can't tell you this.
They showed up at the Bullbash, they had a great time, and they were telling us that the Bullbash
when they showed up, that we were still a year out before they was going to come and do ours.
It was going to be a year because they had some other stores that we were going to convert from
Connecticut front chickens to Popeyes. After the Bullbash, that's such a great time.
Two days later, he calls us, he's back in town, and he tells us that he's went back,
talked his higher-ups, and because of the Bullbash, because of the stuff we hear,
they hear the events we do here, and the people we draw here, they have now moved us to the top of
the list, and we'll be there next door. So, they jumped us in half of those three conversions.
So, it'd probably be spring. They'll probably start ours and sound good.
So, the things you're doing, and it's a community effort, it's a whole, I mean, we can do all this stuff
that you guys, you guys might go as stuff happen. The Bullbash would never happen
if it wasn't for the people in this room, but the stuff you're doing is paying off.
People are noticing this, people want to be here. So, thank you for what you do,
but Bullbash wasn't success because you'd get a business off of it.
It was the win, and we probably...
have a potential to get a couple off of it actually.
That was, I mean, that was, you said everything else thinking.
And we got the toy drive coming up, you know, the Marine's toys for
cops called said they couldn't do it this year.
They didn't have the funds.
So I'm kind of taking that over and got a little team together.
We're taking off with it if you guys want to help, I'd love to help, but we're
going to have to raise the money, we're going to have to distribute the toys, we're
going to have to do the whole thing, then pick up a check today from
Blensia Pop County, a great company that's moved the town, that loves our
mainstream, that loves things we do as well, then we're going to
have to check the day of $10,000 to get that going.
So, I picked it up today.
So, we're not only bringing the businesses in the industry, we're bringing in
great community partners, and it's it's pretty cool to see, so they like our
platform.
Blensia, you use our airport quite a bit, sounds like.
They also paid some sponsorship money to our bullbatch, right?
They also wrote $10,000 to be the child's sponsor of the bullbatch, so they've jumped right in
our community, and really they want to really be a part of it, he told me today, if you need another
check, come back and tell me, so they want to be involved in this stuff, so, of course you don't
want to overdo it, but they're willing to be a partner, you want to use that too.
May I introduce your communication?
I have three, and the first one is kind of bad news, and the other two would be good, so a
different minor, but you know, GRD is increasing our rates a little before I will have a presentation
by Dan Jackson, the dinner rates, three foot, you know, GRD is increasing, so I just want to
get everybody to make them aware and just keep them aware, you know, and then when this
work on some stuff that will make the citizens aware, the second thing is there's going to
need to be some work now on 22nd Street, starting the middle of this week, 22nd Street northeast,
so we're actually going to go in there and replace those culverts, and then do a bunch
of like pothole patching on those large wheel running, but this come, if I had my way, we'd
dig them all out and replace them, but you know, obviously they were able to be shut down for a
lot longer, so we're going to do that whenever we replace those approaches, but to the short-term
picks, we're going to take our pothole patching machine and really patch those, we're going to
replace those culverts, that road doesn't drain real well, so we're trying to get that water
in the drain and keep flowing, so that road will be shut down, we're going to do it,
you know, after everybody gets to work in, you know, in the then school, we'll make this school
and everybody aware of it, but just let everybody know, maybe that car is down different roads to
to close that down for certain times, so it'd be closed for blocks of time, but the evenings will be open,
yeah, so I think what is A to 3, yeah, yeah, so will it be closed for main to D every day or just
the section they're working on, so I'm from Mayday or Mayday or Mayday or Mayday or Mayday.
May it be.
All right.
Each day.
So they'll go north and south.
Well, from the on it, in that county,
there's that orange.
That's ours.
Told you to the tracks.
Yeah.
The tracks.
I'll ask because people are going to ask me.
Yeah.
That's what I'm making the board of work.
Because you guys get a lot of calls and everything.
So we'll re-analyze it to post them on Facebook.
We'll get out of it all the way out.
And best we can.
Just to make everybody wear it.
There's that we will be perfect.
Perfect.
Come with that in here.
Yep.
And probably on the other end of the album.
Well, I was on the album.
And I can tell.
He's going to take two weeks.
I hope not.
And there's something that he knows how I have.
And he's how many big tracks go down there.
I mean, probably in two weeks.
Some of them were running at it.
And we was after a couple weeks ago.
And it was crazy how many big trucks was coming up through there.
And all I think I have.
And this is probably my favorite thing.
Obviously to say is we are going to be doing another big grain amount.
So I'm coming up in November.
So we will have.
We have some people coming in.
It's for our grants.
It's going to be cool.
Well, you're talking about that.
I want to say thank you to everybody that has part in that.
Because towns are sized communities are sized.
They live and die by those things.
And you guys are going to a great job chasing them.
And a great job getting them.
So.
For hours long.
It's.
Yep.
So I appreciate working here in there as I say.
Yeah.
I know not so.
I know so we're going to see these for some things.
Right.
And we're going to...
It's been to god.
And we gotta make one for the power?
I'll hear you work, a bit.
That's all I have.
A bit for you.
Alright 13 adjournment.
Motion.
Thank.
Yeah.
Parker.
Uncle.
He's step.
And part in.
Yeah.
And one.